{
  "questions": {
    "movies": [
      {
        "question": "What movie did Leonardo Dicaprio win an oscar for?",
        "answer": "The Revenant (2015)",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "Name 5 different Leonardo Dicaprio Movies",
        "answer": "Google is your friend!",
        "timeLimit": 20
      },
      {
        "question": "What's the name of the first star wars movie (Episode IV)?",
        "answer": "A New Hope (1977)",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "What's the name of the second star wars movie (Episode V)?",
        "answer": "The Empire Strikes Back (1980)",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "What color was the pill that Neo took in the Matrix?",
        "answer": "The red pill",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "Name three different actors that has played James Bond.",
        "answer": "Sean Connery, George Lazenby, Roger Moore, Timothy Dalton, Pierce Brosnan, Daniel Craig",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "The head of what animal is in the center of an infamous scene from The Godfather?",
        "answer": "A horse",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "For what movie did Steven Spielberg win his first Oscar for Best Director?",
        "answer": "Schindler's List (1993)",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "In Apocalypse Now, Robert Duvall says, “I love the smell of _____ in the morning.",
        "answer": "Napalm",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Alfred Hitchcock thriller is notorious for its shocking “shower scene”?",
        "answer": "Psycho",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "What year was the first Toy Story film released in cinemas?",
        "answer": "1995",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "Who directed Titanic, Avatar and The Terminator?",
        "answer": "James Cameron",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "Meryl Streep won a Best Actress BAFTA for which 2011 political drama?",
        "answer": "The Iron Lady",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of Tom Hanks round-shaped friend in Cast away?",
        "answer": "Wilson",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "Name the film which boasts the famous line: “You can’t handle the truth!”",
        "answer": "A Few Good Men (1992)",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "Name three different Star Wars movies!",
        "answer": "IMDB is your friend!",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "What does Tom Hanks compare life to in Forest Gump?",
        "answer": "A box of chocolates. You never know what you're gonna get.",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "One day Forrest Gump started running, for how long time did he run?",
        "answer": "3 years, 2 months, 14 days and 16 hours",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "In the Avengers movies, what is the name of Thor's hammer?",
        "answer": "Mjolnir",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "Who plays Aquaman in the 2018 movie?",
        "answer": "Jason Momoa",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "He has played both super man and geralt the witcher, what's his name?",
        "answer": "Henry Cavill",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "In what movie does Brad Pitt play Lieutenant Aldo Raine?",
        "answer": "Inglourious Basterds",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "Name three movies of the top 10 highest rated movies on IMDB",
        "answer": "IMDB is your friend!",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "Andy Dufresne (played by Tim Robbins) gets innocently imprisoned for murder in this masterpiece. What's the name of the movie?",
        "answer": "The Shawshank Redemption (1994)",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "What year was the first Godfather movie released?",
        "answer": "1972",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "Who directed the Godfather movies?",
        "answer": "Francis Ford Coppola",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "Name a movie directed by Francis For Coppola EXCEPT the Godfahter movies!",
        "answer": "IMDB is you friend!",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "Which movie has won the highest amount of oscars?",
        "answer": "Titanic, Ben-Hur and The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King, has won the same amount - 11 oscars!",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "What movie is the following quote from: \"A census taker once tried to test me. I ate his liver with some fava beans and a nice chianti\"?",
        "answer": "The Silence of the Lambs (1991)",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "\"I'm gonna make him an offer he cant refuse\". What movie?",
        "answer": "The Godfather (1972)",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the actor that shouted \"You can't handle the truth!\" in A Few Good Men (1992)?",
        "answer": "Jack Nicholson",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "What number is supposedly the meaning of life in The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy?",
        "answer": "42",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "What was in the box in Seven?",
        "answer": "A head",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "\"A former Roman General sets out to exact vengeance against the corrupt emperor who murdered his family and sent him into slavery.\" - what is the movie?",
        "answer": "Gladiator (2000)",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "Who's oldest? Arnold Scharzenegger, Sylvester Stallone or Samuel L Jackson?",
        "answer": "Sylvester Stallone (born 1946)",
        "timeLimit": null
      },
      {
        "question": "Whats wonder womans name as i civilian?",
        "answer": "Diana Prince",
        "timeLimit": null
      }
    ],
    "sports": [
      {
        "question": "What NHL team has the most Stnaley cup wins?",
        "answer": "Montreal Canadiens (24)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which hockey team has won most olympic medals?",
        "answer": "Canada (15)"
      },
      {
        "question": "In what sport can we find names such as Jose Aldo, Anderson Silva and Ronda Rousey?",
        "answer": "MMA"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which boxers faced off in \"The Rumble in the Jungle?\"",
        "answer": "Muhammad Ali and George Foreman"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which England footballer was famously never given a yellow card?",
        "answer": "Gary Lineker"
      },
      {
        "question": "What's Wayne Gretskys nickname?",
        "answer": "The Great One"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many olympic gold medals has Sweden won in ice hockey?",
        "answer": "Two (1994 and 2006)"
      },
      {
        "question": "What does the term \"offside\" refer to in sports such as fotball and ice hockey?",
        "answer": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "How many points is a \"set\" in table tennis?",
        "answer": "11 points"
      },
      {
        "question": "What's the maximum score you can achieve in dart with three darts?",
        "answer": "180"
      },
      {
        "question": "What's super bowl?",
        "answer": "The final game in NFL (National Fotball League)"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many points is a \"perfect game\" in bowling?",
        "answer": "300"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many teams are there in NHL?",
        "answer": "31"
      },
      {
        "question": "Name 5 NHL teams!",
        "answer": "Google is your friend :)"
      }
    ],
    "history": [
      {
        "question": "Through what mountain chain in california goes pacific crest trail",
        "answer": "Sierra nevada"
      },
      {
        "question": "What russian masterpiece was written by leo tolstoj and contains more than 550 000 words?",
        "answer": "War and peace"
      }
    ],
    "geography": [],
    "foodAndDrinks": [],
    "technology": [
      {
        "question": "Whats chinas biggest social network platform?",
        "answer": "Weibo"
      }
    ],
    "games": []
  }
}